[Music]
it is a foregone conclusion that the
pandemic has changed the way we live
as global citizens the effects of covet
19 leaves in its wake many disrupted
industries
many of which now face the next chapter
of their evolution
[Music]
in this latest season of the final pitch
we bring to the fold and new order of
startups
entrepreneurs and innovators whose
mission and reason for being
are closely tied to moving forward and
creating value
in a post-pandemic world
this is the final pitch heroes edition
hoping to back this season's heroes are
a formidable cast
of business and industry leaders the
common thread that binds them all
the ability to spot high impact
entrepreneurs and talent
and the resources to shepherd them
through
these are the investor judges of the
final pitch
from hong kong and macau thailand
indonesia
singapore vietnam malaysia
japan and now the philippines fwd is
breathing new life into the insurance
industry
expanding their product offerings and
focused on creating fresh customer
experiences
with easy to understand products
supported by leading
digital technologies through this
customer-led approach
fwd hopes to achieve its vision to
become the leading pan-asian insurer
that changes the way people feel about
insurance
especially now during this global
pandemic
in joining the final pitch fwd insurance
philippines president and ceo
lee hao zwang is on the lookout for
heroes to join their fold
and help lead the charge towards
revitalizing
the philippine economy fwd is a
pan-asian insurer
we're very young we started in 2013 but
within a short space of time we now
operate across
nine countries time now we have over 50
billion us dollars in assets
in philippines we started in 2014
and now we are one of the top five
insurers in the country and is one of
the fastest
growing we operate nationwide with 17
branches
one of the best capitalized insurers in
the country
our mission in fwd really is to change
the way people feel about
insurance and we do so by being
different in a number of ways
we believe in marrying technology and
the human touch
to create the best possible customer
experience
and because of that we have been rated
number one
customer experience in philippines last
year
by forester research the other way
that we also do it is our singular
obsession
with customer experience for our
distributors
we have built some of the most
professional productive and digitally
connected
advisors to serve and the third we
differentiate ourselves by
using technology to have deep customer
engagement
through our tech platform which is a an
app that customers can
readily connect with us 24 7 or through
our ai enabled call centers
and we continue to do innovations that
push the frontier of our business
you know our main aim also is to be the
employer of choice
and we create different shaded careers
for both our advisors and
for our staff in fwd we offer four main
types of
products and services we have life
protection that covers your life
we have health protection that covers
your critical illnesses and
hospitalization
and the third it's on investment and
saving where we help you
plan for your future for your retirement
for your kids education
and we also have a suite of digital
products that make it really
easy for you to purchase your policies
online with
minimal underwriting it can be done in
minutes
[Music]
i joined fwd because i want to make a
difference i want to do
more i believe insurance can be sold in
a different way in a much simpler way
i believe the customer experience can be
much better than
what it is now and i joined fwd as
a head of agency at a group level
managing
our agency forces across the different
countries so
during that role together with the help
of countries introduced a number of
different
initiatives that significantly raise the
productivity and product professionalism
of our agency force
and because of that the efforts were
recognized and part of that reward is
i get to be here in philippines to run
the business here
i was very privileged to be given this
opportunity to work in philippines
my mission really is to continue this
growth to make sure every single
filipino
is protected and it is our duty to make
sure everyone is covered
number two is to lift to our promise to
change the way people feel about
insurance and that is using
our technical technology dna which is
our strength
married with human touch to our
customers
the pandemic brought out two very
obvious
realization number one is the need for
protection
if something happens to you
you have no backup governments all
around the world
realize that they are not in the
position
to take care of their citizens in this
broad scale pandemic
so which means the private sector have
to step
in the sectors like insurance who can
spread the risk
around who can help in the process of
planning
and helping you know individual
filipinos take charge of their future
you have to think of the future because
the unexpected
may happen to you and you need to be
uh you need to be protected i think one
of the that's one of the key things
after beauty is always on the lookout to
improve
our customer experience so any company
that can help us achieve that mission
we're most interested
in partnering with it can come in the
number of forms
improve our product and services to our
customers
you know you can help us expand our
product offering
or the way we serve them we will be most
interested to talk to you
if it helped us to reach customers that
we couldn't reach before
we're most interested to talk to you
with your tool you can reach
an unreachable segment of customers that
we couldn't reach before or we couldn't
do it
commercially verbally if you can do that
we're most happy to work with you
if you have a way that allows us to hire
more filipinos to give
even better career opportunities we want
to talk to you as well
[Music]
we keep a really open mind because
talent can come from anywhere
opportunity can come from anywhere and
that's why i'm so excited about
final pitch because so many people have
heard about your program and they are
coming in
with really innovative ideas and i
really can't wait
to see all the fantastic ideas that are
being generated
and hopefully you know we will have the
privilege of partnering with one or two
of you
[Music]
up next the unique thing about 917
ventures is that we're part of globe
telecom
globe telecom being the largest mobile
operator in the country with more than
80 million subscribers
and 150 000 corporate clients what we
provide to our startups is to unlock
that unfair advantage
all of these big companies here in the
pandemic a lot of them folded
they had so much fun but it's not about
funds now it's about
the framework to pivot and how to use
this crisis into a new opportunity and
that's what i'd like to contribute
to the final pitch